// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the k-drama about fencing sport?",
    answer: "Twenty Five Twenty One",
    options: [
      "Twenty Five Twenty One",
      "The glory",
      "Island",
      "Cheer Up"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who is the director of Business Proposal K-drama?",
    answer: "Park Seon Ho",
    options: [
      "Kim Sang Woo", 
      "Song Hyeon Wook",
      "Yoon Seong Shik",
      "Park Seon Ho"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the total of seasons in the Naruto original series and Naruto Shippuden series?",
    answer: "26",
    options: [
      "5",
      "220",
      "21",
      "26"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In which year was the K-drama Goblin released?",
    answer: "2016",
    options: [
      "2019",
      "2018",
      "2017",
      "2016"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which character doesn't belong to the Demon Slayer series?",
    answer: "Itachi Uchiha",
    options: [
      "Tanjiro Kamado",
      "Itachi Uchiha",
      "Zenitsu Agatsuma",
      "Nezuko Kamado"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who is director of the Top Gun: Maverick?",
    answer: "Joseph Kosinski",
    options: [
      "Martin Scorsese",
      "Joseph Kosinski",
      "Woody Allen",
      "Spike Lee"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who is the actor who has not played Spider-Man?",
    answer: "Jake Gyllenhaal",
    options: [
      "Tom Holland",
      "Andrew Garfield",
      "Tobey Maguire",
      "Jake Gyllenhaal"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who acted as the Joker in the Joker Hollywood movie?",
    answer: "Joaquin Phoenix",
    options: [
      "Robert De Niro",
      "Glenn Fleshler",
      "Marc Maron",
      "Joaquin Phoenix"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "At the 55th National Film Awards, Taare Zameen Par won 3 awards. Which award doesn't belong to the won awards?",
    answer: "Best Actor",
    options: [
      "Best Actor",
      "Best Film on Family Welfare",
      "Best Lyrics",
      "Best Male Playback Singer"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In which year was the movie Kabir Singh released?",
    answer: "2019",
    options: [
      "2020",
      "2018",
      "2019",
      "2015"
    ]
  },
];